▍2026 美网 女单1/4决赛
佩古拉 3-6 6-4 6-3 纳瓦罗 · 赛后场上采访
First of all, Arthur Ashe Stadium.
首先 阿瑟·阿什球场的观众们
Let's give it up
让我们把掌声送给
for an epic three-setter by Jess Pegula
奉献精彩三盘大战的佩古拉
and Emma Navarro Hearing that crowd
和纳瓦罗 听到现场观众
and them cheering for you.
这样为你欢呼加油
What does that mean Jess?
杰西 这对你意味着什么？
Yeah, it means everything today.
今天 这对我来说就是一切
It was really tough It was physical.
比赛很艰难 体能消耗很大
It's humid We weren't I wasn't exactly
天气闷热 我们 我今天
serving my best and I was fighting a lot
发球并不在最佳状态 还要对抗
of demons out there today
场上冒出的许多负面念头
So thank you guys so much
所以 真的非常感谢大家
for coming out here and it's an honor
来到这里 能在你们面前打球
to play in front of you guys Yeah,
是我的荣幸 是啊
there's there's nothing like it.
真的 没有任何感觉能比得上
It's it's amazing every single time Well,
每一次都这么棒 那么
when I think of your game I think
说起你的比赛 我会想到
about perseverance and what it's taken you
是坚持 是你一路走来
to get to this point Can you share
付出的努力 能不能分享一下
with the crowd what it has taken for you?
走到今天 你付出了什么？
Oh I don't know.
嗯 我也不知道
I think it's just a lot of self -belief I think
我觉得要非常相信自己 我想
that I just really enjoy playing this game
我真的很享受这项运动
and challenging myself every single day
也享受每天挑战自己
to get better I think I I do a great job
让自己进步 我觉得我很擅长
of having a short -term memory So I know
不纠结刚发生的事 所以我知道
that every time I come out no matter what
每一次上场 无论发生什么
I just have to Tell all the the negative me
我都得让那个消极的自己
to shut up and just play tennis and compete
闭嘴 继续打球 继续竞争
and battle and think out there and try
去拼 去思考 尽可能
and problem solve as best I can and Yeah,
找到解决办法 是啊
that's that's all I'm trying to do really well
我真正想做的就是这些
and last thing I won't let you go
最后 先别急着走
without having those conversations with
还得聊聊你和教练团队
your coaching team I know they've left now
那些对话 他们现在已经走了
so they can't defend themselves.
所以没机会替自己辩解了
What was that back -and -forth like
你们这样来回交流
for you guys?
当时是什么感觉？
That's okay. I mean The coach's box
没关系 其实教练席就是这样
is like sometimes you're fighting with them,
有时候你会跟他们较劲
but you're also it's like in a good way,
但这种较劲也有积极的一面
you know It's trying to get you going.
他们想让你振作起来
It's trying to get energy
想让你找到能量
At the same time you're trying
同时你也得努力
to listen get feedback and all this stuff
听进去 获取反馈和建议
So, I mean they've they've all played
他们都打过球
they know what it's like out there
知道身处场上是什么感觉
And so they do a great job
他们做得很好
of supporting me no matter what
无论如何都会支持我
but it doesn't mean sometimes I can get
但这不代表我有时不会
a little annoyed Well, that was fun to watch.
有点烦 看你们互动挺有趣的
Thank you, Jess. Good luck
谢谢 杰西 祝你好运
in your semi -final everyone Give it up
祝半决赛顺利 大家为她鼓掌
for Jessica Pegula into the semifinals.
佩古拉闯进了半决赛